http://www.protapes.com/privacy

download PDF
Pro Tapes & Specialties, Inc.® is committed to protecting your privacy and developing technology that gives you the most powerful and safe online experience. This Statement of Privacy applies to the Pro Tapes & Specialties, Inc.® site and governs data collection and usage. By using the Pro Tapes & Specialties, Inc.® site, you consent to the data practices described in this statement.
Collection of your Personal Information
Pro Tapes & Specialties, Inc.® collects personally identifiable information, such as your email address, name, home or work address or telephone number. Pro Tapes & Specialties, Inc.® also collects anonymous demographic information, which is not unique to you, such as your ZIP code, age, gender, preferences, interests and favorites.
There is also information about your computer hardware and software that is automatically collected by Pro Tapes & Specialties, Inc.®. This information can include: your IP address, browser type, domain names, access times and referring website addresses. This information is used by Pro Tapes & Specialties, Inc.® for the operation of the service, to maintain quality of the service, and to provide general statistics regarding use of the Pro Tapes & Specialties, Inc.® site.
Please keep in mind that if you directly disclose personally identifiable information or personally sensitive data through Pro Tapes & Specialties, Inc.® public message boards, this information may be collected and used by others. Note: Pro Tapes & Specialties, Inc.® does not read any of your private online communications.
Pro Tapes & Specialties, Inc.® encourages you to review the privacy statements of Web sites you choose to link to from Pro Tapes & Specialties, Inc.® so that you can understand how those Web sites collect, use and share your information. Pro Tapes & Specialties, Inc.® is not responsible for the privacy statements or other content on Web sites outside of the Pro Tapes & Specialties, Inc.® and Pro Tapes & Specialties, Inc.® family of Web sites.
Use of your Personal Information
Pro Tapes & Specialties, Inc.® collects and uses your personal information to operate the Pro Tapes & Specialties, Inc.® Web site and deliver the services you have requested. Pro Tapes & Specialties, Inc.® also uses your personally identifiable information to inform you of other products or services available from Pro Tapes & Specialties, Inc.® and its affiliates. Pro Tapes & Specialties, Inc.® may also contact you via surveys to conduct research about your opinion of current services or of potential new services that may be offered.
Pro Tapes & Specialties, Inc.® does not sell, rent or lease its customer lists to third parties. Pro Tapes & Specialties, Inc.® may, from time to time, contact you on behalf of external business partners about a particular offering that may be of interest to you. In those cases, your unique personally identifiable information (e-mail, name, address, telephone number, job title) is not transferred to the third party. In addition, Pro Tapes & Specialties, Inc.® may share data with trusted partners to help us perform statistical analysis, send you email or postal mail, provide customer support, or arrange for deliveries. All such third parties are prohibited from using your personal information except to provide these services to Pro Tapes & Specialties, Inc.®, and they are required to maintain the confidentiality of your information.
Pro Tapes & Specialties, Inc.® does not use or disclose sensitive personal information, such as race, religion, or political affiliations, without your explicit consent.
Pro Tapes & Specialties, Inc.® keeps track of the Web sites and pages our customers visit within Pro Tapes & Specialties, Inc.®, in order to determine what Pro Tapes & Specialties, Inc.® services are the most popular. This data is used to deliver customized content and advertising within Pro Tapes & Specialties, Inc.® to customers whose behavior indicates that they are interested in a particular subject area.
Pro Tapes & Specialties, Inc.® Web sites will disclose your personal information, without notice, only if required to do so by law or in the good faith belief that such action is necessary to: (a) conform to the edicts of the law or comply with legal process served on Pro Tapes & Specialties, Inc.® or the site; (b) protect and defend the rights or property of Pro Tapes & Specialties, Inc.®; and, (c) act under exigent circumstances to protect the personal safety of users of Pro Tapes & Specialties, Inc.®, or the public.
Use of Cookies
The Pro Tapes & Specialties, Inc.® Web site use "cookies" to help you personalize your online experience. A cookie is a text file that is placed on your hard disk by a Web page server. Cookies cannot be used to run programs or deliver viruses to your computer. Cookies are uniquely assigned to you, and can only be read by a web server in the domain that issued the cookie to you.
One of the primary purposes of cookies is to provide a convenience feature to save you time. The purpose of a cookie is to tell the Web server that you have returned to a specific page. For example, if you personalize Pro Tapes & Specialties, Inc.® pages, or register with Pro Tapes & Specialties, Inc.® site or services, a cookie helps Pro Tapes & Specialties, Inc.® to recall your specific information on subsequent visits. This simplifies the process of recording your personal information, such as billing addresses, shipping addresses, and so on. When you return to the same Pro Tapes & Specialties, Inc.® Web site, the information you previously provided can be retrieved, so you can easily use the Pro Tapes & Specialties, Inc.® features that you customized.
You have the ability to accept or decline cookies. Most Web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. If you choose to decline cookies, you may not be able to fully experience the interactive features of the Pro Tapes & Specialties, Inc.® services or Web sites you visit.
Changes to this Statement
Pro Tapes & Specialties, Inc.® will occasionally update this Statement of Privacy to reflect company and customer feedback. Pro Tapes & Specialties, Inc.® encourages you to periodically review this Statement to be informed of how Pro Tapes & Specialties, Inc.® is protecting your information.
Contact Information
Pro Tapes & Specialties, Inc.® welcomes your comments regarding this Statement of Privacy. If you believe that Pro Tapes & Specialties, Inc.® has not adhered to this Statement, please contact Pro Tapes & Specialties, Inc.® at marketing@protapes.com.. We will use commercially reasonable efforts to promptly determine and remedy the problem.
Security & Encryption
Every request placed on the Website is protected by a standard SSL (Secure Socket Layer). This means that the pages you view on our website or forms you submit that should be kept private are and protected from outside intrusions.
Children
The Website is not directed at children. In accordance with federal law, we do not solicit or knowingly collect information from children under age 13 without the verifiable permission of a parent or guardian. If the Company learns that a child under the age of 13 has submitted information online without parental consent, it will not use such information for any purpose (except where necessary to protect the safety of the child or others as required or allowed by law) and will take all reasonable measures to delete such information from its databases by identifying such information for a purge process. If you become aware of any information we have collected from children under 13, please contact us as provided below.
RIGHT TO REMOVAL OF POSTED INFORMATION – CALIFORNIA MINORS
If you are under 18 years of age, reside in California, and have a submitted a form with the Company, you have the right to request removal of unwanted information that you publicly post on the Website or that you submit to Us. To request removal of such information, you can contact marketing@protapes.com.
YOUR RIGHTS IN RELATION TO YOUR PERSONAL DATA
By using the Site, you can exercise the following rights:
I. Refusing To Provide Your Personal Data
The voluntary personal data and Personally Identifiable Information you provide to us is an integral part of your use of the Site. You can choose to forego the provision of that data, but you will be restricted from using our Services.
II. Accessing, Obtaining, Modifying, And Deleting Your Personal Data
If you’d like to remove any information about you that we are storing or that you have provided, you can email us at marketing@protapes.com. After we receive a request to delete any information, we will delete all of your personal data from our systems as quickly as possible. At that point, it will be deleted from our system but kept in encrypted audit files as required by law for a period of up to two years. After that, you will be scrubbed from our audit file backups.
Converting Services
Wide Web Slitting
Wide Web Slitting
Narrow Web Slitting
Narrow Web Slitting
Lathe Slitting
Lathe Slitting
Flexo Printing
